[
  [
    {
      "question": "How many holes are there in a full round of golf?",
      "answer_options": ["9 Holes", "12 Holes", "18 Holes", "Golf isn't a sport"],
      "correct_answer": "18 Holes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the only athlete ever to play in a Super Bowl and a World Series?",
      "answer_options": ["Bo Jackson", "Deion Sanders", "Michael Jordan", "Tim Tebow"],
      "correct_answer": "Deion Sanders"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year was the first Super Bowl played?",
      "answer_options": ["1922", "1954", "1967", "1980"],
      "correct_answer":"1967"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which team did the Chicago Cubs play in the 1945 World Series?",
      "answer_options" : ["Boston Red Sox", "New York Yankees", "Cleveland Indians", "Detroit Tigers"],
      "correct_answer" : "Detroit Tigers"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How many soccer players from each team are allowed on the field at the same time?",
      "answer_options" : ["11 Players", "7 Players", "18 Players", "23 Players"],
      "correct_answer" : "11 Players"
    },
    {
      "question" : "A shuttlecock is used in what sport?",
      "answer_options" : ["Badmiton", "Jai alai", "Cricket", "Shuffle Board"],
      "correct_answer" : "Badmiton"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term is used to describe a baseball game in which a pitcher does not allow any opposing player to reach base for the entire game?",
      "answer_options": ["Yatzee", "Boring", "Aced", "Perfect Game"],
      "correct_answer": "Perfect Game"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is the highest score possible in 10 pin bowling?",
      "answer_options" : ["150", "250", "300", "100"],
      "correct_answer" : "300"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question" : "In which sport can you win the Davis Cup?",
      "answer_options" : ["Golf", "Nascar", "Cricket", "Tennis"],
      "correct_answer" : "Tennis"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How long is an Olympic swimming pool?",
      "answer_options" : ["50 meters", "75 meters", "35 meters", "100 meters"],
      "correct_answer" : "50 meters"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What player was the first to win five straight Wimbledon tennis titles?",
      "answer_options" : ["Serena Williams", "Bjorn Borg", "Andre Agassi", "Roger Federer"],
      "correct_answer" : "Bjorn Borg"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How long must a billiard cue be?",
      "answer_options" : ["75 centimeters", "150 centimeters", "105 centimeters", "90 centimeters"],
      "correct_answer" : "90 centimeters"
    }
  ]
]
